You know I can't turn on
that ferkakta computer!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I left you some brisket
on the kitchen counter!
Thank you!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)Remember
to floss after.
(Mrs Wolowitz:)We have the dentist
in the morning!
(Penny:)Oh, hey.
What's up?
(Amy:)I just wanted to
check in on you.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Amy:)It seems like the
appropriate thing to do
(Amy:)when one's best friend
finds herself replaced
(Amy:)by a smart, beautiful woman
with the smoldering sexuality
of a crouched Bengal tiger.
(Penny:)I already told you,
I'm okay with it.
(Penny:)I mean, if anything,
I'm quite pleased
(Sheldon:)that Leonard
has found someone
(Penny:)that makes him so happy.
(Amy:)It's okay, it's okay.
(Priya:)Thank you.
(Amy:)Now, let's get these
electrodes attached
(Amy:)and see what's going on in that
pretty little noggin of yours.
(Howard:)Okay.